LILLIAN CHENG UI UX Designer

Profile

Enthusiastic UI/UX designer, passionate learner, and a believer in assisting others to find solutions.



(917) 870-7966



lillian.cheng9@gmail.com



www.behance.net/lilliancheng



in progress

Design Skills

Mobile design • Web design • Interaction design • Wireframing and prototyping • User research and user flow • Typography and visual design

Software

Adobe Creative Suite, Adobe XD, Invision

Microsoft Office • Communication and collaboration tools • Mac and Windows

Soft Skills

Problem Solving • Attention to detail • Teamwork • Multitasking • Customer service

Languages

English • Mandarin Chinese • Cantonese

Currently Learning

Figma • Sketch • CSS • HTML • JavaScript



Education

UI Design Certification

2020-Present, UI Immersion & Frontend Development for Designers, CareerFoundry

BA in Psychology

🗰 2020, University of Massachusetts Amherst

Employment History

Associate Clinical Administrative Coordinator

- © Reached out and scheduled Optum HouseCalls service for eligible UnitedHealthcare members
- Answered questions and inquiries for the HouseCalls department,
 documented details of appointments, other inquiries and comments
- Identified, escalated and reported priority issues to the high-level management

Student Work-Study

- 🛱 September 2018-January 2019 | UMass Amherst, Amherst MA
- © Cashier and kitchen staff at Blue Wall, located in campus center
- Hands-on food preparation, helped clean and close the station at the
 end of the shift

Order Processor

- 苗 September 2016-August 2018 | Stanley Black & Decker, E. Longmeadow MA
- Picked merchandise and prepared orders for shipment
- © Performed assigned tasks: Stocked shelves, labeled products, general maintenance etc.
- Worked closely with other shipping divisions (interdepartmental tasks and work)

Hostress

- Responsible for greeting and seating guests, providing menus, monitoring dining areas
- Answered phone calls, took reservations and answered questions from customers

0

Portfolio

